# **OLADELE TEMITOPE FREDRICK**

Ibadan 08145503083 | topefred@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVES**

Looking for work in the industry sector. Interested in QA, technical services, microbiology, R &D, and production. I have a B.Sc. in Microbiology and completed my course work and research for a Masters in Biotechnology and Industrial Microbiology. Also a result driven junior data analyst with 2 years experience in academic and content creation.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### · Gwagwalada Primary health center

April 2016 - September 2016

Microbiologist (Industrial Trainee)

- Label Sample Upon Collection
- Conducted Microbiological Test on the Sample Collected. This Include, Sample Culturing, Fixation, Staining and Microscopic Examination.
- Evaluation of Different Test Results
- Carried out Sterilization Procedures on Laboratory Equipment.
- o Prepared Culture Media
- Carried out Antibiotics Sensitivity Testing
- Carried out different Seriological Tests

### Fredyoung computer concept, Oyo

2019 - 2019

Administrative Manager

- Stored documents in appropriate location
- Maintain log of activities and completed task
- Compare data with source documents
- Compile, sort and verify the accuracy of data before been processed

## Lacturze data analytics

2021 - 2022

Data analyst and content writer

- Compute and analyze data using statistical method
- o Compile statistics from source materials
- o Participate in the publication of data
- Send out surveys
- Code data prior to computer entry
- o Conduct Systematic review of different literatures

### **EDUCATION**

### · University of Ibadan

2021 Industrial Microbiology and Biotechnology MPhil/Ph.d

### University of Abuja

2017
Microbiology
Second Class Upper

### **TECHNICAL (IT) SKILLS**

- · System Administration
- Advanced Microsoft Excel Function

- Google Applications
- MySQL
- Troubleshooting
- Data Quality Assessment
- Data Analysis
- Pattern and Trend Identification

# PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATE

- Introduction to data analysis (Skill share)
- Business analytics (Skill share)
- Joberman soft skill (Jobberman)